All right. Um, but taking a look at the
markets, it's a complete U-turn is what
both the benchmark indices have taken
right now. But shifting focus to the
insurance space then as we have the
August provisional general insurance
data. How have the industry leaders um
and others players have flared in the
month of August. Anorag is here with a
round up. Anorag. So in month of August
as per the provisional figure as per our
sources the general insurance industry
has seen a degrowth of minus 15%. So
month-on-month figure as compared to
July uh uh 2025 to August 2025
uh go digit has seen a degrowth of
minus6%
ICIC Lombard has seen a degus 12% uh new
India assurance
degrowth in premium in comparison to
July in August is of minus 47%
standalone health insurance company NEA
bupa has also seen a degrowth of minus
uh 3.8%
and star health insurance has seen a
degrowth of -6%. So not a good month for
general insurance industry. I'll go
through uh yearon-year number also also
there is a catch in yearon-year number
that last year the long-term premium was
allowed but from 1st of October the
long-term premium is not allowed. So
that is a catch. But in a long-term
yearon-year numbers, uh, industry has
grown up by 4.2% as compared to last
year. ICIC Lombard has grown by 2%. New
India Assurance has shown a growth of uh
9% as compared to last year August 2024.
Go Digit has shown a growth of 13.5% as
compared uh to last year August 2024. Uh
similarly NA bupa and star health also
shown a growth of uh 2%. NAVA bupa 2.74%
and star health 1.85%. So not a good
month for general insurance industry.
The August provisional data is showing a
degrowth in general insurance industry.
>> So concern in the general insurance
industry and that was a quick round up
the August scorecard. Thanks for that.